# Claudiu Vasile

protofoliu-web-en at Freelancer

claudiu.vasile@gmail.com

# Summary

Over 16 solid years in IT support on different OS systems and different IT application, implementation two core banking(Branch Power and Flexcube) and two great applications SAP and Siveco Applications. I'm a team player and sociable person, good communication skill. My objectives are the optimization of the work in my group with more personal involvement in various projects and a personal growth of my skills on UNIX and Windows.

Now, after two year on web developer experience I can make any web full(from start to end) modern application in HTML,PHP,jQuery, ajax API and Javascript on any database server Oracle or MySQL, also developer of Microsoft Excel VBA and APEX Oracle. I have experience work with git and framework like bootstrap, codeigniter, yii, symphony, zend, laravel. I would like to continue with PHP in a big company.

website for web developer:

https://github.com/VasileClaudiu

https://github.com/VasileClaudiu/bootstrap4-responsive

http://vasileclaudiu.github.io/blog/

http://dev-wordpresst.pantheonsite.io

http://dev-minishop.pantheonsite.io

http://dev-my-shop-wordpress.pantheonsite.io

http://www.cartiit.com

http://www.mediator-bucharest.eu

Custom wordpress theme bootstrap 4:

http://www.newuniverses.com/wordpress/

My CV online:

https://vasileclaudiu.github.io/MyCV/

http://www.newuniverses.com/wordpress/mycv

Contact:

Email: claudiu.vasile@gmail.com

Phone: 0771056830 Skype: vasileclaudiu73

# Experience

# Databases Administrator at SC OPCOM SA

#### December 2014 - Present

- System Administrator Oracle Databases
- -Website Administrator www.opcom.ro
- PHP,HTML,Javascript developer on Oracle database, I make Web application for Opcom Company and administration website www.opcom.ro
- Oracle Database 11g: Administration Workshop I Ed 2 -training
- developer of Microsoft Excel VBA

### protofoliu-web-en at Freelancer September 2013 - Present

Hello,

I work in OPCOM Company as website administrator, daily I working in PHP,HTML,JavaScript on database Oracle, I make developer web applications for internal OPCOM.

I used frameworks like Symfony, Yii2, Laravel, Zend, Codeigniter, I used Javascript, Ajax-Api, Angular, database like Mysql, Oracle, Sybase.

I'm a Web Developer with Php,Html,Javascript,JQuery experience, also I can make android applications as android developer. I work with framework like Symfony, Laravel, Code Igniter, Angular and I has been work with cms like Wordpress, Magento. I'm professional great worker, quickly, fast learning, all doing up to done, all job for money, quality hight. I has been work with Android studio, I make some android applications.

#### My web portofolio is:

- -www.atelieruldetuns.ro -backend in laravel sys.atelieruldetuns.ro
- -www.betyjobs.ro -frontend in Codelgniter
- -www.lucrare-licenta.com -backend in zend www.lucrare-licenta.com/comenzi/lucrari-backend
- -www.medasig.md custom php frontend si backend
- -www.rca.md custom php frontend si backend
- -www.setit.ro/tichet -I make wizard javascript
- -www.sitefirma.ro magento
- -www.cartiit.com magento
- -www.alcedoltd.ro/api/application backend in zend I make API server
- -www.opcom.ro Php mentenance

- -www.newuniverses.com Laravel-Vue mentenanta
- -www.newuniverses.com/magento magento 2
- -www.newuniverses.com/forum phpBB
- -www.newuniverses.com/wordpress wordpress
- -www.newuniverses.com/angone/dist -angular laravel CRUD
- -www.newuniverses.com/sym Symfony4 -Rest API Jwt
- -app.obcauction.com -laravel integration Paypal Api, Ninja Invoice
- 188.226.174.88/dist Rest API angular laravel node js Bicoin Bitcoin Core bitcoine-core
- www.newuniverses.com/decebal -/codeigniter CodeIgniter Bootstrap 4,Rest API Jwt , AdminLTE
- www.newuniverses.com/angfirebasechat/www Angular Ionic Chat

#### My Android portofolio is:

- Obcauction

Best Regards,

Claudiu Vasile

Email: claudiu.vasile@gmail.com

Phone: 0771056830 Skype: vasileclaudiu73

# System Engineer-Exchange Administrator at Atos IT Solutions and Services A/S May 2014 - December 2014 (8 months)

System Administrator Exchange 2010:

- Exchange Administrator 2010- windows 2008 server, AD, windows 2012 server.;
- -Migration users and mailbox Exchange 2003 to Exchange 2010 for all clients of Atos Company;
- backup databases exchange 2010;
- Check daily all Environment of exchange 2010 from Atos Company.
- -All help desk for exchange 2010 issue for all clients of Atos Company, resolve all ticket for this issue from SAP interface.

#### System Engineer at Banca Transilvania

May 2007 - November 2013 (6 years 7 months)

IT Areas-IT computer network maintenance, 100 workstations, 7 servers, application development, Visual C #, VBA, fox pro, Visual Fox Pro, Visual Basic, VB Script, ASP Microsoft. Net., Office Aplication (Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Outlook), Microsoft SQL Server 2005, Windows server 2000-2012, Active Directory, Exchange 2010, 2013, PHP, Drupal, Wordpress.

- Configure Backup & restore for Windows, Unix, Linux systems using HP Data Protector;
- Microsoft Windows Server Files Sharing Services security and organization Files Sharing Server;

- Microsoft Windows Server Update Services WSUS Server;
- Microsoft Windows Server SMS Console Services SMS Server:
- Microsoft Windows Server SCOM monitoring alerts;
- Microsoft Windows Server 2003,2008 Active Directory Management and monitoring, managing users and computers;
- 2nd and 3rd level support for clients/of Transilvania Bank employees in IT matters;
- help desk support for over 80 of Transilvania Bank employees;
- Server FTP upload/download;
- branch core banking Branch Power configuration and maintenance-settings reports;
- branch core banking Flex Cube implementing, configuration and maintenance-settings reports;
- hardware maintenance servers, switch, routers, computers, telecommunication.

#### System Engineer

April 2000 - May 2007 (7 years 2 months)

2001-2002 Head of Department Computer-SC Electrica SA -

True Linux Specialization Courses 64;

Specialization Courses Windows 2000 Server and Exchange 2000

Achievement and maintenance network, leased lines (between locations),

achievement dial-up server, ftp server,

server proxy, server http, autocad. proxy server, http server, autocad 2000, autocad 2004.

2003- 2007- Head of Telecommunications Department

- -SAP-configuration and maintenance-settings reports;
- -Siveco Application-COSWIN configuration and maintenance-settings reports;
- -Microsoft Windows Server Files Sharing Services security and organization Files Sharing Server;
- -Squid server configuration;
- -Vsftpd configuration;
- -Samba configuration;
- -Microsoft Exchange 2000 configuration;
- -Linux True 64 configuration;
- -PPPD, Iptables, IPsec;

#### System Engineer

November 1997 - April 2000 (2 years 6 months)

SC Logicnet SA provider, accredited teacher SC ICI SA, SC Logic dialup Internet provider net, teaching courses initially computers (DOS, Windows98, fox, nc, word, excel)

#### Education

English advanced course-Eurocor individual course, 2013 - 2013

Activities and Societies: individual.

Faculty of Electronics and Telecommunications - Bucharest

Bachelor's Degree, Applied Electronics, Computer Systems, 1992 - 1997

# Claudiu Vasile

protofoliu-web-en at Freelancer

claudiu.vasile@gmail.com



Contact Claudiu on LinkedIn